hi ok
girls?
i am an ivg researcher
with two questions,
in fact,
very quickly,
about anxiety and stress.
can be,
swear,
I don't believe it.
man,
which one?
what is your name?
Cecília
Cilia with c
or s r
r c is l a.
well let's go
you think the level of stress and anxiety
from Brazilian
increased or decreased post pandemic?
increased immune?
I don't know if you know,
but recently
was released
1 medicine that combats anxiety and stress
and reduces 85% of women's PMS,
but they aren't seeing it yet.
he is being released by Gisa,
aware of this or not,
he doesn't have the name yet,
it's development.
that's why we're working on it.
it has an anxiolytic effect
which increases dopamine and serotonin.
and I brought you a little sample here
and what do you want to see?
there are four doses of happiness.
do you know the IBGE institute?
Do you know about the IBGE Institute?
is the gourmet Passenger Institute,
nothing old is written,
you see from the side,
right? old?
what a dick face,
man,
here for you this is everything,
beautiful passenger
and reduces to TPM,
anxiety and stress.
yes or no
It is true?
boat here,
for only fifteen reais the box
you can have this Brigadier.
girls,
too much gratitude,
Thanks for the sympathy,
see?
by far
we already realize when people have this energy.
tamo together!